keywordcompetitor.com 2009-01-25

# Privacy Policy

PPC Competitor Reports is committed to safeguarding your privacy on-line. The following statement sets our privacy policy. For the purpose of this Privacy Statement "PPC Competitor Reports" shall mean keywordcompetitor.com. This policy may change from time to time so please re-read this policy periodically. 

Our site collects information in several ways. When you sign up with our PPC Competitor Reports services, you are required to complete an order form. PPC Competitor Reports request your "Contact Information" like your name and email address. 

The Contact Information from the order form is used to register users in our database, and is also used to get in touch with them when necessary. 

You should note that the Contact Information you have provided will not be made publicly available, nor sold to third parties.

PPC Competitor Reports may disclose Contact Information in special cases where PPC Competitor Reports has reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating our terms and conditions of use or may be causing injury or interference with our rights, property, our customers or anyone who could be harmed by such activities. We may also disclose Contact Information when we believe, in good faith, that the law requires it and for administrative and other purposes necessary to maintain services and improve our products and services. 

Our site has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. We use SSL secure server with digital certificates (https://) and all personal information is fully encrypted during all transactions. Please note, however, that no data transmission over the Internet is completely secure. As a result, while we attempt to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you provide to us and you transmit such information to us at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission we attempt to ensure the security of your personal information on our systems. 

You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your password and account and are fully responsible for all activities that occur using your password or account. Please notify us immediately of any unauthorized use of your password or account or any other breach of security. PPC Competitor Reports will not be liable for any loss that you may incur as a result of any third party's use of your password or account, either with or without your knowledge. You may not use anyone else's password at any time. 

If you wish to review or update your account details, simply sign-in to your account and click the “My Account" link found on the upper right corner of the PPC Competitor Reports Search Bar, or if you are on the result page, simply click the “Update Profile” link which will lead you to our password protected Members' Area. You may update your information any time. Should you encounter problems with updating your profile, please send an email to [support@keywordcompetitor.com ](mailto:support@keywordcompetitor.com%20) , and our Support Team will be glad to assist you. 

If at some point in the future, there is a change to our privacy policy that will affect your personal information; we will notify you by email of the relevant changes. 

If you have any questions about this Privacy Statement, the practices of this site or your dealings with this website, please email our Customer Care Department at [support@keywordcompetitor.com ](mailto:support@keywordcompetitor.com%20) .
